I ain't want nothing. I'm about to go to sleep, but I just wanted to say, fuck you to this dude.
I think, you know, it's really wild when people are calling me a tourist for bringing humanitarian aid to Cuba or bragging.
How is this bragging?
I'm going to tell you this.
Folks are like, oh, you're going to have a great time.
It's going to be a great experience.
What are we talking about?
Do you know what the experience is?
Bringing aid to the Cuban people.
That's the experience.
And not only bringing aid, but human to human connection.
Helping people feel seen, which is what all humans really be wanting.
I don't give a damn if it's a good experience or a shitty experience.
Because that's not the purpose of the experience.
I am merely a vessel.
That's what this is about.
And like I said here, whose comrade are you?
Not mine.
Prick.
Some of y'all really need to learn a thing or two about learning a thing or two.
It's got to be a better way.